{"programming": [{"wrong": [], "question": "Write a Java program called Max2Numbers that prompts user for three integers, and prints out the top two maximum numbers.\n\nExample 1:\nEnter the first integer:  3\nEnter the second integer: -1\nEnter the third integer:  1\n\nMaximum numbers: 3, 1\n\nExample 2:\nEnter the first integer:  10\nEnter the second integer: 11\nEnter the third integer:  10\n\nMaximum numbers: 10, 11\n\nExample 3:\nEnter the first integer:  2\nEnter the second integer: 2\nEnter the third integer:  2\n\nMaximum numbers: 2, 2", "correct": []}, {"wrong": [], "question": "*****Test Question that is not multiple choice or True/False", "correct": []}], "questions": [{"wrong": ["T"], "question": "If a Java source file is compiled successfully, the compilation produces one or more files with a .java extension", "correct": ["F"]}, {"wrong": ["F"], "question": "In Java, the identifiers main, Main, and mAin are all distinct.", "correct": ["T"]}, {"wrong": ["T"], "question": "String literals in Java can be enclosed in either single quotes(\u2019) or doublequotes(\"), or three of each(\u2019\u2019\u2019 or \"\"\").", "correct": ["F"]}, {"wrong": ["F"], "question": "A keyword is a predefined identifier in Java.", "correct": ["T"]}, {"wrong": ["T"], "question": "A valid Java identifier (variable) such as the name of a class must begin with an alphabetic character.", "correct": ["F"]}, {"wrong": ["T"], "question": "All if statements must include an else branch.", "correct": ["F"]}, {"wrong": ["F"], "question": "!(x == 0) and x != 0 are logically equivalent boolean expressions for integer value x.", "correct": ["T"]}, {"wrong": ["F"], "question": "The operator = is used for assignment and initialization but not to test for equality.", "correct": ["T"]}, {"wrong": ["F"], "question": "In Java, a float takes 4 bytes of memory.", "correct": ["T"]}, {"wrong": ["F"], "question": "In Java, indentation is not significant.  It is simply a strict convention used for readability and considered good programming etiquette.", "correct": ["T"]}, {"wrong": ["static", "void", "public"], "question": "Which of the following is not a keyword in java?", "correct": ["Bool"]}, {"wrong": ["private method", "static method", "finalize method"], "question": "Which of the following methods is executed first before execution of any other thing that takes place in a program?", "correct": ["main method"]}, {"wrong": ["-128 to 127", "-2147483648 to 2147483647", "None of the mentioned"], "question": "What is the range of short data type in Java?", "correct": ["-32768 to 32767"]}, {"wrong": ["-32768 to 32767", "-2147483648 to 2147483647", "None of the mentioned"], "question": "What is the range of byte data type in Java?", "correct": ["-128 to 127"]}, {"wrong": ["*", "#", ">"], "question": "Which of following symbols is used to indicate a comment in Java?", "correct": ["//"]}, {"wrong": ["myExtraLongVariableName", "_employee_id", "___university", "June1997__"], "question": "Of the following, which is a valid Java identifier?", "correct": ["All of the above are valid identifiers."]}, {"wrong": ["A variable is a \u201cline\u201d of code in the body of a program, which may change.", "A variable is a word that has a special meaning to the compiler.", "A variable is a collection of eight bits.", "A variable is a structured, general-purpose language designed primarily for teaching programming."], "question": "Which of following statements best describes a variable and its primary purpose?", "correct": ["A variable is a named storage location in the computer\u2019s memory used for holding a piece of information."]}, {"wrong": ["boolean b4 = \u2018true\u2019", "boolean b2 = \u2018false\u2019;", "boolean b1 = 1;"], "question": "Which one is a valid declaration of a boolean?", "correct": ["boolean b3 = false;"]}, {"wrong": [":=", "=", "equal"], "question": "Which of the following is the correct operator to compare two integer variables?", "correct": ["!="]}, {"wrong": ["Operation", "None of the above", "Statement", "Variable"], "question": "In programming terms, a sequence of characters inside a set of double quotation marks is called:", "correct": ["String literal"]}, {"wrong": ["1 and 4", "1, 2, 3, and 4", "3 and 2"], "question": "With x = 0, which of the following are legal lines of Java code for changing the value of x to 1? \n1. x++;\n2. x = x + 1;\n3. x += 1;\n4. x *= 1;", "correct": ["1, 2, and 3"]}, {"wrong": ["dollars = pennies % 100\ncents = pennies / 100", "dollars = pennies // 100\ncents = pennies / 100", "dollars = pennies // 100\ncents = pennies % 100"], "question": "Which of the following statements determines the dollars and cents of a variable in terms of pennies?", "correct": ["dollars = pennies / 100\ncents = pennies % 100"]}, {"wrong": ["&&", "||", "=="], "question": "Which of the following operators is used to invert a conditional statement?", "correct": ["!"]}, {"wrong": ["!b && x == 1", "b || x == \u22121", "x == 1 || x == \u22121"], "question": "Suppose that b is false and x is 0. Which of the following expressions evaluates to true?", "correct": ["!b || b"]}, {"wrong": ["I only", "II only", "III only", "I and II only"], "question": "Assume that a, b, and c are of variables of type int. Consider the following three conditions.\n\nI. (a == b) && (a == c) && (b == c)\nII. (a == b) || (a == c) || (b == c)\nIII. (a - b) * (b - c) * (a - c) == 0\n\nWhich of the conditions above is (are) always true if at least two of a, b, and c are equal?", "correct": ["II and III only"]}, {"wrong": ["false"], "question": "Evaluate the following Java expression by giving true or false values. 0 >= 0", "correct": ["true"]}, {"wrong": ["true"], "question": "Evaluate the following Java expression by giving true or false values. 15 < 2 && 12 > 3", "correct": ["false"]}, {"wrong": ["false"], "question": "Evaluate the following Java expression by giving true or false values. 6 != 5", "correct": ["true"]}, {"wrong": ["false"], "question": "Evaluate the following Java expression by giving true or false values. 5 < 10 || 8 > 20 && 4 < 2", "correct": ["true"]}, {"wrong": ["false"], "question": "Evaluate the following Java expression by giving true or false values. !(12 == 12 && 4 > 6)", "correct": ["true"]}, {"wrong": [], "question": "What is the value of the variable z after the following code snippet?\nint x = 3;\nint y = 6;\nint z = x - y * 2;", "correct": ["-9"]}, {"wrong": [], "question": "What are the values of x and y, respectively, after the following code snippet?\nint x = 21;\nint y = 6;\nif (x%y > y && y > 0) {\n    y = 20;\n    x = y ;\n}\nSystem.out.println(\"x = \" + x + \", y = \" + y);", "correct": ["x = 21, y = 6"]}, {"wrong": [], "question": "What is the value of this Java expression\n((.2 * 10)/4) ?", "correct": ["0.5"]}, {"wrong": [], "question": "What is the value of the Java expression \n(.2 * (10/4)) ?", "correct": ["0.4"]}, {"wrong": [], "question": "What are the value of price, after the following code snippet?\ndouble cost = 52;\nif (cost < 50){\n    cost = cost + 10;\n}\nif (cost > 40){\n    cost = cost * 2;\n}\nif (cost < 100){\n    cost = cost - 20;\n}\nSystem.out.println(\"cost = \" + cost);", "correct": ["cost = 104.0"]}, {"wrong": [], "question": "What are the exact outputs, after the following code snippet?\nint a = 1;\nint b = 2;\nint c;\nint d;\nc = ++b;\nd = a++;\nc++;\nb++;\n++a;\nSystem.out.println(a + \" \" + b + \" \" + c);", "correct": ["3 4 4"]}, {"wrong": [], "question": "What are the exact outputs, after the following code snippet.\ndouble var1 = 1 + 5;\ndouble var2 = var1 / 4;\nint var3 = 1 + 5;\nint var4 = var3 / 4;\nSystem.out.println(var2 + \" \" + var4);", "correct": ["1.5 1"]}, {"wrong": [], "question": "What is the value of the variable num1 after the following code snippet?\nint num1 = 200;\nif (num1 < 200){\n    if (num1 < 50) {\n        num1 = num1 - 5;\n    }\n    else{\n        num1 = num1 - 10;\n    }\n}\nelse{\n    if (num1 > 150){\n    num1 = num1 + 5;\n    }\n    else{\n    num1 = num1 + 10;\n    }\n}\nSystem.out.println(\"num1 = \" + num1);", "correct": ["num1 = 205"]}, {"wrong": ["x = 5;", "x = 3;", "x += 1;", "x++++;", "x *= 2;", "x -= 1 + 2;"], "question": "*****Make x's value 2, assume x's current value is 0:", "correct": ["x = 2;", "x += 2;", "x = 2 % 3;"]}, {"wrong": [], "question": "*****Fill in the blank test:", "correct": ["Correct"]}]}